Guide to the Oehrlein and Associates Architect records, 1981-2007 MS2294
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Project files, 1981-2007; Series 2
  - GSA-Interior Building - HSR [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 18th and C Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1917 Charles Butler Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Interior Building - HSR [2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - GSA-Justice Bldg HSR, 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 950 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1934 Zantziner, Borie & Medary Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Lafayette Building - HSR [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 811 Vermont Avenue NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1940 Holabird & Root Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Lafayette Building - HSR [2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GSA-Veterans Building - HSR, 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 810 Vermont Avenue NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1920 Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Veterans Building - HSR [ 1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - GSA-Veterans Building - HSR [ 2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - GSA-Veterans Building - HSR - History, 1988; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Harpers Ferry National Park, 1990; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation of Building #36, site surveys and other studies Address: Harpers Ferry National Park, WVA Folder contains photographs
  - Healy Hall, Georgetown University, 1996; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Exterior Stabilization/Restoration Address: 3700 O Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1879 Smithmeyer & Pelz Folder contains photographs
  - Holy Trinity Church, Wash DC, 1998; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Preservation consulting for rehabilitation Address: 1325 36th Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Homer Building [1 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Exterior and lobby rehabilitation Address: 601 13th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1913-1914 Appleton P. Clark, Jr. Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Homer Building [2 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Homer Building [3 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Homer Building [4 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Howard Hall, Howard University, 1997; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration/Interior Rehabilitation Address: 2400 6th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1868 Folder contains report and drawings and photographs
  - Howard Hall, Howard University [1 of 3], 1997; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Howard Hall, Howard University [2 of 3], 1997; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Howard Hall, Howard University [3 of 3], 1997; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [1 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 451 7th Street SW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1965 Marcel Breuer Folder contains original building specs, report and photographs
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [2 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [3 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [4 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [5 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [6 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development [7 of 7], 1996; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development photos [1 of 2], 1996; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development photos [2 of 2], 1996; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dept of Housing & Urban Development photos Specifications and Bidding Forms, 1996; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hyattsville Armory, 1986; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation and addition mixed use project including office, retail, theater Address: 5340 Baltimore Ave, Hyattsville MD Original date of construction and Original architect: 1918 Wm. Harris Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [1 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [2 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [3 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [4 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [5 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hyattsville Armory photos [6 of 6], 1986; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Irvings Sporting Goods, 1989; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Research/preliminary design Address: 1001-1003 E Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1928 Folder contains photographs and research data
  - Kiosks on the Mall, 1999; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Design/construction of 4 new visitor kiosks Address: Washington, DC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1999 Oehrlein & Assoc Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Kiosks on the Mall photos [1 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Kiosks on the Mall photos [2 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Kiosks on the Mall blueprints, 1999; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Langston Golf Course, 1992; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Renovations Address: 2600 Benning Road NE, WDC Folder contains drawings
  - The Lansburgh's Site, 1989; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Exterior Rehabilitation Address: 7th and D Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1916 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Lincoln Square, 2001; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Façade Rehabilitation/Storefront Design Address: 11th & F Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1880-1920 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Lincoln Square negatives, 2001; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Square 1013 E St, 503 11th St. photos [1 of 2], 2001; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Square 1013 E St, 503 11th St. photos [2 of 2], 2001; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln Square 511 11th St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Square 1012 F St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lincoln Square 1009 E St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Square 1007 E St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Square 1005 E St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln Square 525 11th St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Square 523 11th St. photos, 2001; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lincoln Theater, 1991; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Address: 1215 U Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1921 Reginald Geare Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Lincoln Theater, 1991; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Maryland State Monument, 1993; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Type of work: HABS Measured Drawings/Photography Address: Antietam National Battlefield, MD Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Mayflower Hotel, 1985; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Address: 1127 Connecticut Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1925 Warren Wetmore contains photographs
  - Miller Farm HSR, 1992; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: Antietam National Battlefield, MD Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Museum of Natural History Rotunda photos, 1998; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Address: 10th & Constitution Avenue NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1910 Hornblower & Marshall Folder contains 1915 report and drawing and photographs:
  - Museum of Natural History Rotunda transmittals, 1998; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - National Geographic, 1994; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Exterior Repairs Address: 1145 17th Street NW, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Old Admin Bldg, Arl Nat Cemet, 1994; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Repairs to Fire Damage Address: Arlington National Cemetery, VA Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Old Masonic Temple (see 901 F Street), 1993; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6--8)
  - Oriental Building Association, 2002; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Condition Survey/Recommendations Address: 600 F Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1909 Albert Goenner Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Otto Farmhouse HSR, 1993; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - P Street Bridge, 1991; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Historic Structures Report Address: P Street at Rock Creek Park Original date of construction: 1935 Folder contains drawings and old dwgs, photographs and report
  - P Street Bridge Research, 1991; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Historic Structures Report Address: P Street at Rock Creek Park Original date of construction: 1935 Folder contains drawings, photographs, and report
  - Park Tower, 1986; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration/Lobby Rehabilitation Address: 2440 16th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1929 William Harris Folder contains photographs
  - Patent Office Building, 2002; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Preservation Architects for Exterior Restoration/Interior Rehabilitation Address: 8th and F Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1836-67 William Elliot, Robert Mills, Thomas U Walter Folder contains photographs
  - Patent Office Building photos [1 of 3], 2002; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Patent Office Building photos [2 of 3], 2002; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Patent Office Building photos [3 of 3], 2002; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Patent Office Building photos [1 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Patent Office Building photos [2 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Patent Office Building photos [3 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Patent Office Building photos [4 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Patent Office Building photos [5 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Patent Office Building photos [6 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Patent Office Building photos [7 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Patent Office Building photos [8 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Patent Office Building photos [9 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Patent Office Building photos [10 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Patent Office Building photos [11 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Patent Office Building photos [12 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Patent Office Building photos [13 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Patent Office Building photos [14 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Patent Office Building photos [15 of 15], 2002; Series 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Postal Square (City Post Office), 1992; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Preservation Architects for Exterior Restoration/Interior Rehabilitation Address: 2 Massachusetts Avenue NE, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1914 Daniel Burnham Folder contains photographs
  - Potomac Annex-Elevators, 1994; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Elevator Repairs Address: 23rd & E Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1904-07 Ernest Flagg Folder contains photographs
  - Red Cross Building Dismantling, 1999; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Dismantling Documents for building Address: 1730 E Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1915 Trowbridge & Livingston Folder contains photographs
  - Ritz Carlton Balconies, 1991; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 2100 Massachusetts Ave NW, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Ritz-Carlton Hotel, 1983; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Repairs and Addition Address: 2100 Massachusetts Ave NW, DC contains drawings and Photographs/brochure
  - Rock Creek Golf Course, 1999; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Renovation Address: 16th & Rittenhouse Sts NW, WDC Contains Drawings:
  - Shakespeare Theater Offices, 1997; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration/Interior Rehabilitation Address: 516 8th Street SE, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Sherrick Farmstead HSR, 1994; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Southeast Federal Center, 1982-1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Historic Preservation Analysis/Environmental Impact Statement Address: North Capitol & Wash Navy Yard SW Folder contains Historic drawings and photographs
  - Southeast Federal Center, 1982-1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Southern Building, 1987; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 15th & H Streets NW, DC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1912 Daniel Burnham Folder contains photographs
  - Square 321, 1991; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Address: 1114-1118 F St/1101 E St NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Square 428/810-826 7th St NW, 1990; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 810-826 7th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1927 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council, 2002; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Address: 5th and E Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction: c1840-1924 Folder contains Historic drawings and photographs
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [1 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [2 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [3 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [4 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [5 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [6 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council photos [7 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Square 488/Nat Research Council loose [8 of 8], 2002; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Square 529/704 3rd St NW, 1989; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Preliminary Design Address: 704 3rd Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - St. Elizabeths Barns/Stable/Design Guidelines, undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation/Design Guidelines Address: St. Elizabeths West Campus Folder contains reports and photographs
  - St. Elizabeths Barns/Stable/Design Guidelines photos, undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - St. Elizabeths Barns/Stable/Design Guidelines booklets, undated; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - St. Matthew's Court photos, 2007; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation of historic townhouses Address: 1717-25 Rhode Island Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction: c1880-1910 Folder contains photographs
  - St. Matthew's Court photos [1 of 2], 2007; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - St. Matthew's Court photos [2 of 2], 2007; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - St. Matthew's Court original drawings [1 of 2], 2007; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - St. Matthew's Court original drawings [2 of 2], 2007; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - State Department Elevators, 1997; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Preservation Architects for Elevator Repairs/ Upgrades Address: 2201 C Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Strathmore Hall Arts Center, 1986; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Exterior Renovation Address: 10701 Rockville Pike, Rockville, MD Original date of construction and Original architect: 1899 Appleton P. Clark, Jr. Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Straus Fountain photos [1 of 2], 1997; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Dismantling/Restoration/Reconstruction Address: 1300 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs/report
  - Straus Fountain photos [2 of 2], 1997; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Dismantling/Restoration/Reconstruction Address: 1300 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC contains drawings and Photographs/report
  - Sumner School / Magruder School photos, 1983; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Design/CDs for rehabilitation Address: 1201 17th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1872 Adolph Cluss Folder contains mylar drawings/negs and Photographs/report
  - Sumner School / Magruder School photos, 1983; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Design/CDs for rehabilitation Address: 1201 17th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1872 Adolph Cluss Folder ontains mylar drawings/negs and Photographs/report
  - Sumner School / Magruder School photos, 1983; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Design/CDs for rehabilitation Address: 1201 17th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1872 Adolph Cluss contains mylar drawings/negs and Photographs/report
  - Sun Building, 1990; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Condition Survey Address: 1317 F Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1885 Alfred B. Mullett Folder contains photographs and report
  - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier photos [1 of 2], 1989; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Study for Repairs/Supervision of Repairs Address: Arlington National Cemetery, VA Original date of construction: 1932 Folder contains photographs and glass negatives
  - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier photos [2 of 2], 1989; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier final report, 1989; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Tower Building, 1986; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Dismantling documents for clock tower Address: Baltimore St & Guilford Ave, Balt, MD Original date of construction: 1910 Folder contains photographs and report
  - Tower Building photos [1 of 2], 1986; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Tower Building photos [1 of 2], 1986; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - US Court of Military Appeals, 1984; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Historic structures report Address: 450 E Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1910 Elliott Woods Folder contains photographs
  - US Courthouse Annex, 2000; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Preservation architects for addition to courthouse Address: 333 Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1952 Louis Justement Folder contains photographs and brochure
  - US Courthouse Annex, 2000; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - US Courthouse Annex historic report, 2000; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - US Treasury North Wing - "Fire", 1996; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Historic structures report Address: 15th & Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1836-1869 Robert Mills, Thomas U. Walter, Ammi B. Young, Isaiah Rogers, A.B. Mullett Folder contains drawings and photographs and original report
  - US Treasury North Wing - "Fire", 1996; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - US Treasury North Wing - "Fire" photos [1 of 3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - US Treasury North Wing - "Fire" photos [2 of 3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - US Treasury North Wing - "Fire" photos [3 of 3], 1996; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Victor Building, 1999; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Consulting for Exterior Restoration Address: 9th and H Streets NW, WDC
  - Washington Monument, undated; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Address: 14th & Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1884 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Washington Monument, undated; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Washington Monument Lodge, 2002; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Research/preliminary design Address: 14th & Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1888 Folder contains photographs
  - West Heating Plant, 1995; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Address: 1051 29th Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs and paint anal.
  - Westory Building, 1990; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 607 14th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1906 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - White House Visitors Center, 1992; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation of Baldrige Hall, Commerce Building for use as visitor center Address: 1401 Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1932 York & Sawyer Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Women in Military Service to America Foundation Memorial Hemicycle Restoration, 1990; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Site Investigation Report and Specifications for Hemicycle Restoration Address: Arlington National Cemetery, VA Original date of construction and Original architect: 1933 McKim, Mead and White Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Woodward & Lothrop Dept Store, 1987; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 1025 F Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1901-1926 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Worthington House HSR, 1994; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: Monocacy National Battlefield, MD Folder contains photographs
  - Miscellaneous (PADC Annual Reports), undated; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Slides Volume 1 (General- Ellipse Visitor Center), undated; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Slides Volume 1 (Franklin School- Gallaudet), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Slides Volume 1 (Gallery Row-Healy Hall), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Slides Volume 1 (Hecht Company-Howard Hall), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Slides Volume 2 (IRS Building-901 F. Street), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Slides Volume 2 (Old Post Office-Ritz Carlton), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Slides Volume 2 (Smithsonian A&I-Smithsonian Castle), undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Slides Volume 3 (SE Federal Center-1001 Pennsylvania Ave.), undated; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Slides Volume 3 (Tariff Building-US Capitol), undated; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Slides Volume 3 (Victor Building-Woodward & Lothrop), undated; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Oversize photos of various sites, undated; Series 2 (Box 47)